Vedran Arnautovic

Senior UX Designer

527 Brunswick Street Fitzroy North VIC 3068

phone 0434 490 076 web vedran.io email hello@vedran.io twitter @vedranio

I'm a user centred designer equally comfortable in the minutiae of pixel detail and ambiguity of early product discovery. I focus on UX design, usability, interaction design and user research. I can code (a little).

I get a kick out of working with passionate teams, seeing people interact with the products I design, and making those interactions more intuitive and useful.

Experience

SEEK

Jan 2014 - present

Senior UX Designer

I've led design on key initiatives within SEEK's advertiser portfolio, often crossing over both sides of the marketplace.

My work is a mixture of tactical projects where I closely work with small agile teams, and more strategic efforts where I've worked with senior leaders to define the future of SEEK's products.

Freelance

Sep 2016 - present

Freelance UX designer

Gymsales

I lead design for Gymsales, working closely with the CEO and the dev team.

Rubicon

I ran a design sprint for Rubicon's Dutch clients and developed a prototype for the solution we came up with during the sprint.

Kolektiv

Over 6 months, I coached Kolektiv's product team on usability testing and lean UX practices.

SMS

Sep 2010 - Jan 2014

Consultant (UX designer and BA)

- UX Designer and BA (NAB)
- UX Designer (NAB)
- Interface Designer and BA (BP)

Internally, I was appointed the Customer Experience (CX) lead for Victoria kickstarted the development of our CX capability.

Leica

Feb 2009 – Sep 2010 Melbourne

System Design Engineer & BA

Upon returning to Melbourne, I worked with Leica's software team to define design improvements based on my field research.

Leica

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009 London

System Design Engineer

A career shaping opportunity allowed me to spend two years researching how our clients and support teams interacted with our instruments, and to use those findings to design better solutions for them.

Vision BioSystems

Jan 2004 - Feb 2007

Software Engineer

I started out very technical, developing software for medical devices. Working in an organisation with no designers created a window of opportunity to start designing and show initiative to test software with users.

Education

Univ. of Melbourne

1999 - 2004

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

Bachelor's degree, Mechatronics

Tools

Sketch, Adobe CC, Marvel, Invision, Axure, Morae, Principle, Framer.js, CSS, HTML, Javascript, Github

+ anything else I need to learn.

page 2/2